[{"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e80", "question": "During what war was the novel \"The Short-Timers\" set?", "answer": "Vietnam War", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59e6b5f9fb6c85e9e634ff46", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed \"Land of 10,000 Lakes\"?", "answer": "Minnesota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b6d", "question": "Who won a Best Supporting Actor Oscar for the 2004 movie \"Million Dollar Baby\"?", "answer": "Morgan Freeman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffb5d885dad637d903c8824", "question": "The southernmost city in the world is located in which country?", "answer": "Argentina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133916e", "question": "What the are the first names of \"The Brothers Coen\"?", "answer": "Joel and Ethan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b018", "question": "What Spanish explorer conquered Montezuma and the Aztecs?", "answer": "Hernando Cortes", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe3eac538e4e5d4832e6315", "question": "On which day of Creation did God make the land and seas?", "answer": "Third", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5990f4cffa5fdd6dd25324e6", "question": "Central African Republic shares its northern border with mostly which country?", "answer": "Chad", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2a3", "question": "What does the Roman numeral C represent?", "answer": "100", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8c4", "question": "What Parisian hill is home to the Moulin Rouge and the Sacr\u00e9-C\u0153ur Basilica?", "answer": "Montmartre", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe6a89d20565ad31a57c7f8", "question": "Who was the first sitting U.S. President to ride a train?", "answer": "Andrew Jackson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff14380b0ee8c595b6d39b2", "question": "Who wrote the 15th century novel \"The Tale of Two Lovers\"?", "answer": "Pope Pius II", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339963", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is Moe's last name?", "answer": "Szyslak", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c24f", "question": "What do you call the feeling of having experienced something before?", "answer": "Deja vu", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392d5", "question": "What British rock-and-roll legend recorded a 1975 album titled \"Venus and Mars\"?", "answer": "Paul McCartney", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133990f", "question": "What Rolling Stones song did VH1 rank as the greatest song in rock\u00ad and \u00adroll history?", "answer": "Satisfaction", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c61d", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Chlorine?", "answer": "Cl", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6014c6d1fbde8045e48466ba", "question": "What is the cause of Lyme disease?", "answer": "The bite of blacklegged ticks infected with Bacterium\u00a0Borrelia burgdorferi\u00a0or rarely, bacterium Borrelia mayonii.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600b87561d8c1817608d53e8", "question": "Why does cheddar cheese need a bandage?", "answer": "It\u2019s aged longer -- Instead of wax, a bandage made of cloth is used to help the cheese \"breathe\" while it's in long-term storage.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6fd", "question": "What was the better known name of the old 91 meters sprint race?", "answer": "100 yards", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b093", "question": "What large amphitheater in Rome was opened to showcase gladiator combat?", "answer": "The Colosseum", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6000ed209a72b906b34e3ce9", "question": "Fissures, vents and plugs are all associated with which geological feature?", "answer": "Volcano", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a000", "question": "What British TV series featured Eddie \"Fitz\" Fitzgerald and Jane \"Panhandle\" Penhaligon?", "answer": "Cracker", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133949f", "question": "Who played the role of Mayor Randall Winston on the TV show \"Spin City\"?", "answer": "Barry Bostwick", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0d2", "question": "What guitar player was the last act to perform at the original Woodstock in 1969?", "answer": "Jimi Hendrix", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa5743c73aa70ea0b70b34", "question": "Which U.S. state has the motto \"Equal Rights\"?", "answer": "Wyoming", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ba7", "question": "What museum, designed by Frank Lloyd Wright, was opened in 1959?", "answer": "Guggenheim Museum", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133addb", "question": "Who was the first US president to have a woman serving in his cabinet?", "answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a66e", "question": "What river do the Holland Tunnel and Lincoln Tunnel pass beneath?", "answer": "Hudson River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6014c580fbde8045e48466ae", "question": "When hyenas gather, what are they called?", "answer": "Cackle -- Many people refer to them as a clan of hyenas, which is equally acceptable, but the proper term is cackle.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398b0", "question": "The Golden Globe Awards honor excellence in which two industries?", "answer": "Movie and television", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e0a", "question": "What 1984 hit repeats the phrase \"Come on, shine your heavenly body tonight\"?", "answer": "Lucky Star", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397d0", "question": "What type of music did Patsy Cline sing?", "answer": "Country music", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b9f", "question": "What 1996 movie earned Sean Penn his first Oscar nomination?", "answer": "Dead Man Walking", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad31", "question": "Elizabeth Bowes-Lyon was better known by what name?", "answer": "The Queen Mother", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398e7", "question": "What US university was the setting for the 1973 movie \u201cThe Paper Chase\u201d?", "answer": "Harvard", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7cc5c877e98cb97778a23", "question": "Which city was the first capital of Japan?", "answer": "Nara", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dce", "question": "What two Rocky III costars won the final match of the very first WrestleMania?", "answer": "Mr. T and Hulk Hogan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b3236a0bf195a31e15d73bd", "question": "What geologic period is also known as the \"Age of Fish\"?", "answer": "Devonian period", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a883", "question": "What Blue Ridge peak in North Carolina is the highest point east of the Mississippi?", "answer": "Mount Mitchell", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a270", "question": "Who was the female lead in the 1967 film \"Barefoot in the Park\"?", "answer": "Jane Fonda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aab", "question": "Who said, \"Do give books - religious or otherwise - for Christmas\"?", "answer": "Lenore Hershey", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5e72ccfcd0874f1a5e2d1c26", "question": "What is a \"Winkle Picker\" or \"Winklepicker\"?", "answer": "An English long pointed shoe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b4bef49076251badbeaca", "question": "Which U.S. President had his sister initially serve as First Lady?", "answer": "Grover Cleveland -- \u00a0His sister Rose Cleveland took on the duties of First Lady until he married his bride Frances in June 1886.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1e3", "question": "When first published, what was the original intent of the \"Michelin Guide\"?", "answer": "To boost the demand for cars and tires", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b27b", "question": "What African region has been ravaged by militia called the Janjaweed?", "answer": "Darfur", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6014c712fbde8045e48466bd", "question": "What is the medical term for goosebumps?", "answer": "Horripilation -- The word is derived from the Latin words \"horripil\u0101ti\u014d\" (bristling of hair) and \"horripil\u0101re\" (to shudder).", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397b8", "question": "What TV sitcom opens with the theme \"Making our Dreams Come True\"?", "answer": "Laverne and Shirley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fde5107c6c6b019850c9a8c", "question": "Mariner IV sent the first pictures of which planet back to Earth?", "answer": "Mars", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015e977fe83fe1f2a824be7", "question": "Who was the Confederate spy who became a bodyguard for the Pope at the Vatican?", "answer": "John Surratt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7c5", "question": "Who won a Nobel Prize for discovering Insulin?", "answer": "Frederick Banting", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fca", "question": "Which Canadian province is the setting for the novel \"Anne of Green Gables\"?", "answer": "Prince Edward Island", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7761feec85e375820b317", "question": "Where is the Valley of the Moon?", "answer": "Jordan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "592eada3f83302ff91e4647f", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Nebraska?", "answer": "Lincoln", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5d2", "question": "How many claws does a domestic cat have?", "answer": "18", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a86d", "question": "Where in England is the Stonehenge monument located?", "answer": "Wiltshire", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c46c", "question": "What bird lays its eggs in other birds' nests?", "answer": "Cuckoo", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339916", "question": "What was the name of Vince Vaughn\u2019s gymnasium in \u201cDodgeball: A True Underdog Story\u201d?", "answer": "Average Joe's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937eab508d98002fdd633a7", "question": "Easter Island is part of which South American country?", "answer": "Chile", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c824", "question": "What pet bird takes its name from Australian Aborigine words for \"good eating\"?", "answer": "The budgerigar", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394ed", "question": "What member of Fleetwood Mac released a 1981 solo hit single titled \"Trouble\"?", "answer": "Lindsey Buckingham", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa3d33c73aa70ea0b70af4", "question": "Who was the state Louisiana named after?", "answer": "King Louis XIV of France -- Explorer Ren\u00e9-Robert Cavelier named the area to honor his king. \"La Louisiane\" translates to \"Land of Louis\".", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59071bc23745b36be73039c4", "question": "What is the only food that cannot give Tony Chu a psychic sensation in the comic series \"Chew\"?", "answer": "Beets", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e1c", "question": "What TV show's announcer was Hank \"Hey Now!\" Kingsley?", "answer": "The Larry Sanders Show's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c51", "question": "Who starred in the lead male role in the 1968 movie \"Planet of the Apes\"?", "answer": "Charlton Heston", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c929", "question": "What is a bactrian?", "answer": "Two-humped camel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338df5", "question": "What Broadway team collaborated on \"Flora the Red Menace\" before writing \"Cabaret\" and \"Chicago\"?", "answer": "John Kander and Fred Ebb", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393dd", "question": "What is the real first name of the singer Boy George?", "answer": "George", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aedd", "question": "Who was president of the US from 1953 to 1961?", "answer": "Dwight D. Eisenhower", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a17b", "question": "What comic strip character is Beetle Bailey's sister?", "answer": "Lois", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aafa", "question": "Which country borders Chad to the north?", "answer": "Libya", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a627", "question": "Which state is directly south of Virginia?", "answer": "North Carolina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398b6", "question": "What movie stars Marlon Brando as a boxer who stands up against a corrupt union?", "answer": "On the Waterfront", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7cd", "question": "What route runs from Chicago to Los Angeles?", "answer": "Route 66", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339222", "question": "As a child, what did Casper the Friendly Ghost die from?", "answer": "Pneumonia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fec8945ec223966ae8f8827", "question": "The tagline \"Justice has its price\" comes from which 1998 movie?", "answer": "\"A Civil Action\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5aab2eda58d116dab4aecb43", "question": "Who played Wayne Szalinski's wife in the 1989 film \"Honey, I Shrunk the Kids\"?", "answer": "Marcia Strassman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7cb", "question": "What republic is located between Lithuania and Estonia?", "answer": "Latvia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fec86bcec223966ae8f8811", "question": "Who was the first female artist in history to have 4 consecutive singles from one album reach the Top 5 in the Billboard Hot 100?", "answer": "Cyndi Lauper's 1983 classic \"She's So Unusual\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c954", "question": "Who was the first American scientist to win a Nobel prize?", "answer": "Albert Michelson", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59e802b1de59ea584496fe98", "question": "Which singer had a hit with the song \"Hand on Your Heart\" in 1989?", "answer": "Kylie Minogue", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339847", "question": "Who released the album \"I Got Dem Ol' Kozmic Blues Again Mama\"?", "answer": "Janis Joplin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c40b", "question": "Where do bumblebees normally nest?", "answer": "Underground", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb80", "question": "Which one of tennis' Grand Slam tournaments did Pete Sampras never win?", "answer": "French Open", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9f6", "question": "What takes place in Happy Valley, Hong Kong?", "answer": "Horse racing", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dc4", "question": "By including cannon fire in his play, Henry VIII, Shakespeare caused the 1613 fire that destroyed what building?", "answer": "The Globe Theatre", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5da", "question": "In which city does the White Nile meet the Blue Nile?", "answer": "Khartoum", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4b9", "question": "Ivory is made up of what substance?", "answer": "Dentin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8ad3101dd7bf43be5e777", "question": "Who invented the color wheel?", "answer": "Sir Isaac Newton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c34d", "question": "The strength of prescription eyeglasses is measured in what unit?", "answer": "Diopters", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a91c", "question": "In what US state would you find Fort Point?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397b4", "question": "What wise guys are forever linked to the phrase: \"Nyuk, nyuk, nyuk\"?", "answer": "The 3 Stooges", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8d5", "question": "Which meteorological phenomena means \"a curl of hair\" in Latin?", "answer": "Cirrus clouds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a445", "question": "Which country shares borders with China, US, Finland and Ukraine?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a0", "question": "What movie starred Johnny Depp as Willy Wonka?", "answer": "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0f7", "question": "Who was assassinated at the Lorraine Motel in Memphis,Tennessee?", "answer": "Martin Luther King Jr.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a1d", "question": "What M-word means the words at the bottom of a coat of arms?", "answer": "Motto", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600cc1bb6de0eb824d4052e2", "question": "What Islands make up the U.S. Virgin Islands?", "answer": "The U.S. Virgin Islands consist of Saint Croix, Saint Thomas, Saint John, and Water Island, alongside 50 other tiny islets.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c84", "question": "Who joined Alicia Keys on the 2002 hit song \"Gangsta Lovin'\"?", "answer": "Eve", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a54c", "question": "What river flows into the Pacific Ocean between Oregon and Washington?", "answer": "Columbia River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "597cd467e347d002c297e4af", "question": "Who was the first monarch of the House of Windsor?", "answer": "George V", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394f8", "question": "Who hosted \"The Daily Show\" before Jon Stewart?", "answer": "Craig Kilborn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339924", "question": "Who was the host of TV\u2019s \u201cUnsolved Mysteries\u201d?", "answer": "Robert Stack", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a13", "question": "What was Ralph Kramden's weekly salary as a bus driver on \"The Honeymooners\"?", "answer": "$62", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a647", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Colorado?", "answer": "Denver", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339351", "question": "What was Ray's occupation on the TV show \"Everybody Loves Raymond\"?", "answer": "Sports writer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397e8", "question": "Which boat\u00a0passed through the Sea of\u00a0Green, the Sea of Holes and\u00a0the Sea of Time?", "answer": "The Yellow Submarine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e40", "question": "What was the real name of TV's \"Mr. WIzard\"?", "answer": "Don Herbert", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59675e9d2b59efe0e9417e98", "question": "What two states are bordered by more states than any other?", "answer": "Tennessee and Missouri", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5febaee37e83c707845b20f8", "question": "What year was the first black hole discovered?", "answer": "1971", "category": "science"}, {"id": "60062afcc9d816e292245c1c", "question": "What American artist preferred to call his sculptures \"structures\"?", "answer": "Sol LeWitt\u00a0came to fame in the late 1960s with his wall drawings and \"structures\" but was prolific in a wide range of media.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5989a867cb8751d53e7d75fa", "question": "United States' observation of Mardi Gras was started in which city and state?", "answer": "Mobile, Alabama", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b92c", "question": "How much does it cost to buy a utility in a standard game of Monopoly?", "answer": "$150", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c45f877e98cb9777899e", "question": "Which country was known as South West Africa until 1990?", "answer": "Namibia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be21", "question": "George Fox is traditionally called the founder of what religious group?", "answer": "The Quakers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7caa1877e98cb97778a08", "question": "In which country will you find the cities Toledo and Granada?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae3c", "question": "During what decade did the Charleston become the dance craze?", "answer": "1920s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a38", "question": "The \"Tuesday Club Murders\" was a novel written by what mystery writer?", "answer": "Agatha Christie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "601b4c9b49076251badbead8", "question": "Who was the first American to orbit the Earth?", "answer": "John Glenn -- He orbited the Earth three times in five hours in a Mercury space capsule he named \"Friendship 7\".", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff51d1fff04d658268c9322", "question": "The world's first postage stamp was introduced in what year?", "answer": "The world's first postage stamp, which featured a portrait of Queen Victoria, was introduced by Great Britain in 1840.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1c2", "question": "Which artist married Carrie Fisher in 1983?", "answer": "Paul Simon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133984b", "question": "The music duo \"Daft Punk\" consists of which two French musicians?", "answer": "Thomas Bangalter and Guy-Manuel de Homem-Christo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5990f44efa5fdd6dd25324df", "question": "Which classical composer wrote the Hungarian Rhapsodies?", "answer": "Franz Liszt", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe3ec888b5801b8f54a7fad", "question": "Where in England was the Magna Carta signed in 1215?", "answer": "A Field Near Runnymede", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bd6", "question": "Who was the messenger of the Roman Gods?", "answer": "Mercury", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffcfb3d9dc5ec6cd98a8315", "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?", "answer": "Leonardo da Vinci", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a60d", "question": "Which country has the world's largest protected nature reserve?", "answer": "Greenland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6000ed7f9a72b906b34e3cec", "question": "Who discovered the mathematical system of logarithms?", "answer": "John Napier", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6008d9b9f4f3bc4a292f8611", "question": "When did the Mayflower reach America?", "answer": "The Mayflower landed along the shores of Cape Cod on November 11, 1620.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fffa77173838c5c8a417f38", "question": "What are people who love eating ice called?", "answer": "Pagophagiacs", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391b9", "question": "Who directed the movie \"Blade Runner\"?", "answer": "Ridley Scott", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af48", "question": "In which year did Louis Reard invent the bikini?", "answer": "1946", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8f9", "question": "What type of animal was selected to test out the first electric toothbrush?", "answer": "A dog", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9f6", "question": "What Sponge cake is baked in the form of a female digit?", "answer": "Lady Fingers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bb0", "question": "Who played the title role in the 1980 comedy film \"Private Benjamin\"?", "answer": "Goldie Hawn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909d31dbb53d1af6588650f", "question": "What year did the TV special \"A Charlie Brown Christmas\" made its debut on CBS?", "answer": "1965", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d1f", "question": "What sport is the focus of the movie \"The Color of Money\"?", "answer": "Pool", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c64e", "question": "What must a mole do every four hours so it doesn't die?", "answer": "Eat", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e6e", "question": "Who played the blind character in the movie \"Red Dragon\"?", "answer": "Emily Watson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef5a016ce05a3942286e08", "question": "When Dwayne Wade briefly left the Miami Heat starting in 2016, which NBA team did he sign with?", "answer": "Chicago Bulls", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1f6", "question": "Hoa Lo Prison was more commonly called what by American POWs?", "answer": "The Hanoi Hilton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe699cf20565ad31a57c74b", "question": "What was the U.S. Hush Hush in World War II?", "answer": "Admiral Nimitz's Jeep", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8aa6b01dd7bf43be5e75a", "question": "What\u2019s another name for a footrest?", "answer": "Ottoman", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abc0", "question": "Tirana is the capital of which European country?", "answer": "Albania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9ac", "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Canada?", "answer": "Logan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5e38d36bf6c8a670a7957c5a", "question": "The United States shares a land border with how many countries?", "answer": "Two", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe6a1c120565ad31a57c7a6", "question": "Which US president delivered the first televised inaugural address?", "answer": "Harry S. Truman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58ab949d86faa38a764be50e", "question": "What company made the LFA?", "answer": "Lexus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a97c", "question": "What nation's legislative body is named The Storting?", "answer": "Norway", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a897", "question": "What city is home to the Rose Tower?", "answer": "Dubai", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1e5", "question": "Who is Tippi Hedren's daughter?", "answer": "Melanie Griffith", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015ff61fe83fe1f2a824c4e", "question": "In 1948, which NBA basketball team did the Harlem Globetrotters defeat which eventually helped break the NBA's color barrier?", "answer": "Minneapolis Lakers", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd3e", "question": "What holiday is celebrated with an aluminum pole, the Airing of Grievances, and Feats of Strength?", "answer": "Festivus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd66638a5bfecdd737e0867", "question": "What color is second from the top in a rainbow?", "answer": "Orange", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f02", "question": "In what film is the real name of \"the Bride\" revealed to be Beatrix Kiddo?", "answer": "Kill Bill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394d9", "question": "What is D.J.'s full name on the TV show \"Roseanne\"?", "answer": "David Jacob", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd2c", "question": "In what sport are the Beaters in charge of batting away the Bludgers?", "answer": "Quidditch", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecc122ec223966ae8f8865", "question": "The 1982 football game that birthed \"The Play\", was between which schools?", "answer": "Stanford and Berkeley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c743", "question": "What is the more common term for amblyopia?", "answer": "Lazy eye", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6017372e44491cbd7c5a1785", "question": "During the American Civil War, what ship engaged the iron-clad ship USS Monitor off Hampton Roads, Virginia?", "answer": "On March 9, 1862, the USS Monitor engaged the CSS Virginia in a naval battle that resulted in a draw.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea3636ff048f679a45ab0a", "question": "What country has the world\u2019s most ancient forest?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a44f", "question": "The path known as \"Silk Road\" stretched for 4,000 miles from China to where?", "answer": "Rome", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5937ea4108d98002fdd633a0", "question": "For which film did Anthony Quinn win an Oscar for Best Suporting Actor in 1957?", "answer": "Lust for Life", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bf3", "question": "Which comic book hero lives in the city of Metropolis?", "answer": "Superman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a9b", "question": "What English author wrote the 1923 book \"Kangaroo\"?", "answer": "D.H. Lawrence", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c337", "question": "Which grow faster - fingernails or toenails?", "answer": "Fingernails", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a686", "question": "Which three states share a border with Michigan?", "answer": "Indiana, Ohio and Wisconsin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb4a", "question": "What is the name for Germany's high-speed highways?", "answer": "Autobahn", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7b0", "question": "What river forms most of the border between the US states Georgia and Alabama?", "answer": "Chattahoochee river", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339689", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is the name of Mr. Burns' stuffed bear?", "answer": "Bobo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600cc8816de0eb824d4052fc", "question": "What is Camp David's official name?", "answer": "Naval Support Facility Thurmont -- President Eisenhower named it Camp David after his grandson, David.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad4", "question": "What creatures does an ichthyologist study?", "answer": "Fish", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5989aee8cb8751d53e7d7618", "question": "What is the largest North American country by land area?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7f3", "question": "On what continent were the Boer Wars fought?", "answer": "Africa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5c90d01652800b05cac20f0d", "question": "In what city was Bruce Lee born in?", "answer": "San Francisco, California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "590681c6ff9c0647b50a8097", "question": "Under what name did Nintendo re-release the Nintendo Entertainment System in 2016?", "answer": "Nintendo Entertainment System: NES Classic Edition", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abb6", "question": "Lilongwe is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Malawi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b08b", "question": "What company, founded in 1885, is the oldest telecommunications company in the US?", "answer": "AT&T", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adcb", "question": "Who succeeded Stalin as Communist Party leader?", "answer": "Nikita Khrushchev", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c29", "question": "How old was Walt Disney when he died in 1966?", "answer": "65", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4b0", "question": "Balsam, Fraser, and Douglas are all types of what?", "answer": "Firs", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ad6", "question": "Dustin Hoffman earned his first Oscar nomination for what movie?", "answer": "The Graduate", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1d4", "question": "Who ordered the disastrous \"Great Leap Forward\" in 1958?", "answer": "Mao Tse-tung", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600e0e381d348e9c6eed4815", "question": "How many people (military and civilians) in the Soviet Union died from World War II.", "answer": "Approximately 27 million people died as a result of the war, which represented 15% of the population of the country.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5904a4f5cf93664eb10486c7", "question": "What are the nicknames of the twin sisters who work as enforcers for Darcy Parker, in the \"Strangers in Paradise\" comic series?", "answer": "Tambi and Bambi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a5b", "question": "What American poet wrote: \"The fog comes on little cat feet\"?", "answer": "Carl Sandburg", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4b6", "question": "What process includes the following phases: prophase, metaphase, anaphase, and telophase?", "answer": "Cell mitosis", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdf0", "question": "What fitness program did Judi Sheppard Missett create in 1969?", "answer": "Jazzercise", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396de", "question": "Which pop group was initially named \"The Pendletones\"?", "answer": "The Beach Boys", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be6a", "question": "What is Indianapolis Speedway also known as?", "answer": "The Brickyard", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a15", "question": "What was the title of the 2003 Russell Crowe movie that was subtitled \"The Far Side of the World\"?", "answer": "Master and Commander", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b46801dd7bf43be5e7bf", "question": "What Marvel superhero was created to sell orange juice?", "answer": "Captain Citrus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5f4", "question": "Chevrolet sold a souped-up version of what car as the \"Z24\"?", "answer": "The Cavalier", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7347aeec85e375820b235", "question": "Which US presidents signed the Declaration of Independence?", "answer": "Thomas Jefferson and John Adams", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3ca", "question": "What is the largest island in the Atlantic?", "answer": "Greenland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c762", "question": "When gathered in a group, what bird species are called a \"murder\"?", "answer": "Crows", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca7d", "question": "What is the common name for the Aurora Borealis?", "answer": "Northern lights", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600395cf57a0e35c43f83896", "question": "What is the term for a three-dimensional composition made from a variety of traditionally non-artistic materials and objects?", "answer": "Assemblage", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c08b", "question": "Toxiphobia is the irrational fear of what?", "answer": "Being poisoned", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59029d5acad1ec93f27df74c", "question": "Where did Thomas Lipton open his first grocery store?", "answer": "Glasgow, Scotland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2d7", "question": "What military legend was nicknamed \"Light Horse Harry\"?", "answer": "Henry Lee", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba6b", "question": "Who was the number 1 ranked male tennis player the most years during the 1970\u2019s?", "answer": "Jimmy Connors", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea4653ff048f679a45aba1", "question": "What kind of muscle contraction is also referred to as \"static tension\"?", "answer": "Isometric", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ab", "question": "Who does Emma Watson play in the Harry Potter films?", "answer": "Hermione", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339432", "question": "Who was Charlie's roommate in the 1989 movie \"Dead Poets Society\"?", "answer": "Richard", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a69d", "question": "The Shenandoah Valley is located in which eastern US state?", "answer": "Virginia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601b4b6649076251badbeac4", "question": "Maya Angelou spoke at the inauguration of which U.S. President?", "answer": "Maya Angelou recited her poem \"On the Pulse of Morning,\" at President Bill Clinton's first inauguration in 1993.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a1e1e25b5a031299b74573f", "question": "Which present-day country in the Southern hemisphere did the Dutch reach in 1606?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339531", "question": "What show debuted in 1963 and became the longest running sci-fi series?", "answer": "Doctor Who", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd971fd23c87fd04dd15e4f", "question": "During World War II, what famous company produced propaganda films for the U.S. government?", "answer": "Walt Disney Productions", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a56d", "question": "Which US capital city was originally called Le Fleur's Bluff?", "answer": "Jackson", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea43f3ff048f679a45ab8b", "question": "What is the name of the submerged fringe of a continent?", "answer": "Continental Shelf", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f3f", "question": "What acoustic track was the only number one hit for 1990s hard-rock band Mr. Big?", "answer": "To Be with You", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601600bbfe83fe1f2a824c57", "question": "Who took the first color photograph in the world?", "answer": "Scottish physicist James Clerk Maxwell created the first color photograph on May 17, 1861.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b465", "question": "Who ordered Atlanta be burned in 1864?", "answer": "General Sherman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ae9431574a5ce6b56b8244", "question": "What job did Agatha Christie's second husband do?", "answer": "Archaeologist", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdfbe7d003d27d341092bcf", "question": "Which South American city is laid out in the shape of a puma?", "answer": "Cusco, Peru", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd96df723c87fd04dd15e31", "question": "What job did Queen Elizabeth II have during World War II?", "answer": "Auto mechanic", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3cf", "question": "What area of the Atlantic is said to be responsible for the disappearance of ships and aircraft?", "answer": "Bermuda Triangle", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fef597d6ce05a3942286e04", "question": "How old was Miley Cyrus when she first auditioned for the role of \"Hannah Montana\"?", "answer": "11", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefc0f56ce05a3942286f0b", "question": "What is the name of the French ship in the film \"Master and Commander: Far Side of the World\"?", "answer": "Acheron", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392cf", "question": "What film stars Bruce Willis as a plastic surgeon Ernest Menville?", "answer": "Death Becomes Her", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdaba4a0b8cce1e6fda7057", "question": "What cheese's name literally means \"recooked\" in Italian?", "answer": "Ricotta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e8a8745404ad935a7e1a63d", "question": "According to the commercial, how many licks does it take to get to the center of a tootsie pop?", "answer": "Three - A one a two a three *crunch*", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be91", "question": "Who hit .202 with three homers while playing outfield for the Birmingham Barons in 1994?", "answer": "Michael Jordan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b382", "question": "Is kissing under the mistletoe comes from whose customs?", "answer": "Druids", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0f8", "question": "Who was the second Toronto Blue Jay player to lead the American league in home runs?", "answer": "Fred McGriff", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e147ab46ca6dac04a20ca50", "question": "Who plays the character \"Eleven\" in the TV show \"Stranger Things\"?", "answer": "Millie Bobby Brown ", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c550", "question": "What word for a part of the eye is also the name of the Greek Goddess of the Rainbow?", "answer": "Iris", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c105", "question": "What is the meaning of the Latin phrase \"cum grano salis\"?", "answer": "With a grain of salt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea83bfff048f679a45ac2a", "question": "How many known moons does Pluto have?", "answer": "5", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fd8", "question": "What TV show did \"Young Americans\" spin off from?", "answer": "Dawson's Creek", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339677", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is the name of Springfield's music store?", "answer": "King Toot's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc21", "question": "What year was the construction of the Eiffel Tower completed?", "answer": "1889", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c37b", "question": "Which English sci-fi writer first conceived the idea of artificial communication satellites in 1945?", "answer": "Arthur C. Clarke", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fede3d16ce05a3942286dd7", "question": "Who was the voice of Mr. Potato Head in \"Toy Story\"?", "answer": "Don Rickles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb8c", "question": "How many total combined red and black numbers are there on a roulette wheel?", "answer": "36", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c19c", "question": "What nationality is tennis player Martina Hingis?", "answer": "Swiss", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bddd", "question": "What children's game takes its name from the Swahili word for \"build\"?", "answer": "Jenga", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4d993e08b8581f80b092b4", "question": "What critically, and commercially successful indie game released in 2017, borrowed its art style from 1930s cartoons?", "answer": "Cuphead", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3b2", "question": "What is the heaviest breed of bear?", "answer": "Polar bear", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338910", "question": "Which nursery rhyme character \"kissed the girls and made them cry\"?", "answer": "Georgie Porgie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5f1649f3f9b80650dbe7f92b", "question": "Which country music artist was the runner-up on the 21st season of the TV show \"Survivor\"?", "answer": "Chase Rice", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe1f1cb145fb29466707394", "question": "What British automobile company made a car called the Super Snipe?", "answer": "Humber", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339acf", "question": "Who plays Adam Sandler's boss in the 2006 film \"Click\"?", "answer": "David Hasselhoff", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0e2", "question": "Which types of pasta have a large cylindrical shape?", "answer": "Cannelloni and Paccheri", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e910598d7247dfc0fa00313", "question": "What year was the element Berkelium discovered?", "answer": "1949", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c41e", "question": "What are baby Koalas called?", "answer": "Joeys", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6a3", "question": "Which state is located on the northern border of Pennsylvania?", "answer": "New York", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a962", "question": "How many territories does the US administer over?", "answer": "16", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c90c", "question": "What is a calm ocean region near the equator called?", "answer": "Doldrums", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe4e8a806d333868d34d74c", "question": "Where can you find Pont Du Gard, part of an ancient Roman aqueduct?", "answer": "N\u00eemes, France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fbaed8f0738315b1fb74e31", "question": "What spell was used to trick the Goblet in \"Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire\"?", "answer": "Confundus Charm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133904f", "question": "Who composed \"Peter and the Wolf\"?", "answer": "Sergei Prokofiev", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3eb", "question": "What is the highest point in the United States?", "answer": "Denali (formerly Mt. McKinley)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6010ca3e0775fa611bce67f5", "question": "What common medical apparatus was designed using aerosol hairspray as an inspiration?", "answer": "Inhaler -- Developed in the 1950s by Riker Laboratories president George Maison for his daughter who suffered from asthma.", "category": "general"}]